A Guide to the Papers of Henry Evans Howell, Jr. 1948-1976
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University Libraries, Old Dominion University
- Political Papers 1948-1973
  - Sub-Series L: 1973 Gubernatorial Campaign
    - Prison Reform, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Prisons in Virginia (1968-1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Prisons - Green Springs Controversy, 1973 (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 12)
    - "Public Protectors," (1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Regional Government - "Federal Regional Councils" (Melvin B. Mogulof), (1970), 1973 (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Registration Statistics (1969-1971), 1973 (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Research Center for Virginia (1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 16)
    - "Right to Work" Law, 1973 (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 17)
    - "Right to Work" Law - C.O.P.E. Materials, 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Publication of National Right to Work Committee, August-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 2)
    - ROTC (1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Rubicon - DOOR (Drug Program), (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Rubicon - DOOR (Drug Program), (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Scheduling - "An Analysis of the Rural Vote for 1973 Scheduling Purposes" (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Securities Exchange Act (1970), 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Senior Citizens (1969-1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Senior Citizens, 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Senior Citizens - American Association of Retired Persons Publications (1970-1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Senior Citizens - Virginia Rules for Nursing Homes, 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Senior Citizens - "Tax Relief for the Aged in the New River Valley" (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Senior Citizens - Industrial Gerontology (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Senior Citizens - Miscellaneous U.S. Government Publications, 1969-1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Small Claims Courts (National Institute for Consumer Justice Study) - I (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Small Claims Courts (NICJ Study) II (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Small Claims Courts (NICJ Study) III (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Small Claims Courts (NICJ Study) IV (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Solid Waste Management - ("The State's Role in S.W.M."), (1971), 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 6)
    - State Employees - Civil Service (1965-1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 7)
    - State Employees - Pay Raise and Retirement Matters, 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 8)
    - State Employees - Personnel Policies, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 9)
    - State Employees - Retirement System (Police), (1969-1970), 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 10)
    - State Employees - Retirement System (Holdings as of December 31, 1965), 1973 (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 11)
    - State Employees Retirement System (Holdings as of December 31, 1969) (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 1)
    - State Employees - Salary Study (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 2)
    - State Government, Reorganization (1966-1971), 1973 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 3)
    - State Government, Reorganization, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 4)
    - State Government, Reorganization (Misc. Publications), (1964-1967), 1973 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Strip Mining, 1973; Fiscal Prospects and Alternatives, 1974 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Taxation, 1971-1973 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Taxation (1967-1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Taxation - ABC Plan, 1973 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Taxation - Rolling Stock and Personal Property Taxes, A Comparative Analysis (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Taxation - Sales Tax, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Taxation - State Level (Study re: Kentucky Taxes) (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Taxation - State Level (Study re: Kentucky Taxes), (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Taxation - State and Local Taxation (Misc. Studies), (1967-1968), 1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Tourism, 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Tourism - Virginia Historical Landmarks, 1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Tourism - Misc. Data on Virginia, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Transportation (1969-1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, 1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Transportation - Howell Position Paper from 1969 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Transportation - Misc. Studies, 1967-1972 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Transportation - Misc. Studies, Virginia, 1971-1973 (Box-folder Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Transportation - Air (1961-1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Transportation - Rail, 1969-1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Transportation - Water (1968,1971),1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Transportation - Mass Transit, 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Transportation - Public Transportation Needs in Virginia Metropolitan Areas (I), (1971), 1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Transportation - Public Transportation Needs in Virginia Metropolitan Areas (II), (1971), 1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Veterans, 1969-1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam and AMB (1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (Miscellaneous Reports), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Revision of Constitution, 1973 (Box-folder Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Democratic Party, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Virginia General Assembly, 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Virginia - Miscellaneous Data, 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Republican Party, 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Voter Participation and Registration (1968-1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Voter Registration - Effort to Extend Hours for Registering (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Voter Registration - "First Vote" Effort (1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Water Authority (Roanoke), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Water Pollution Problems (1966-1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Water Resources, 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Welfare (1969), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Welfare - Annual Reports, Virginia Department of Welfare (1967-1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Welfare - Public Welfare Laws (Virginia), (1968,1972), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Women's Rights, 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Women, Virginia Commission on the Status of (First Report),(1971), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Zip Codes (Virginia), 1973 (Box-folder Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Henry Howell Private Schedule: Long Range Projections, 1973 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Henry Howell Private Schedule, September-October, 1972 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Henry Howell Private Schedule, November-December, 1972 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Henry Howell Private Schedule (Incomplete), January-May, 1973 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Henry Howell Private Schedule (Incomplete), June-July, 1973 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Henry Howell Private Schedule, August 1973 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Henry Howell Private Schedule, September 1973 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Henry Howell Private Schedule, October-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Henry Howell Public Schedule (Incomplete), March-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Henry Howell Appearances, Correspondence re: December 1971- September 1972 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence re: Henry Howell Appearances, October 1972 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence re: Henry Howell Appearances, November- December 1972 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence re: Henry Howell Appearances, January-March, 1973 (Box-folder Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence re: Henry Howell Appearances, April-May, 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re: Henry Howell Appearances, June 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence re: Henry Howell Appearances July 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re: Howell Appearances August 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re: Henry Howell Appearances September 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence re: Howell Appearances October-November 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Requests for H.E.H. Appearances December 1971-August 1972 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Requests for H.E.H. Appearances September 1972 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Requests for H.E.H. Appearances October 1972 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Requests for H.E.H. Appearances November-December 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Requests for H.E.H. Appearances January-April 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Requests for H.E.H. Appearances May 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Requests for H.E.H. Appearances June-October 1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Tentative H.E.H. Appearances, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances March, August-September 1972 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances October-December 1972 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances January-February 1973 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances March 1973 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances April 1973 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances May 1973 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances June 1973 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances July 1973 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances August 1973 (Box-folder Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances September 1-10, 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances Sept. 11-20, 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances Sept 21-30,1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances October 1-15, 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Regrets re: Requests for H.E.H. Appearances October 16 - November 3, 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Mrs. Henry Howell - Private Schedule, April-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence re: Betty Howell Appearances, April-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Mary Howell - Private Schedule (Incomplete) August - November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence re: Substitute Speakers June-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Advertising - Proposal by Matthias and Redmond Agency, December, 1972 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Advertising - Correspondence with Lois Holland Calloway Agency, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Advertising - "Buy Time" (Lois Holland Calloway), 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Advertising - "Cash Flow" (Lois Holland Calloway), 1973 (Box-folder Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Automatic Data Processing - Misce1laneous Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Canvassing - Miscellaneous Records (Norfolk), 1973 (Box-folder Box 128, Folder 2)
    - "Direct Mail" (Form Letters) 1973 (Box-folder Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Polling (Howell Poll) - Part I September 1973 (Box-folder Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Polling (Howell Poll) - Part II September 1973 (Box-folder Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Polling - Miscellaneous Data March-September 1973 (Box-folder Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Telephones, Campaign Use of January 1973 (Box-folder Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Voter Registration, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 128, Folder 8)
- SERIES IV: LEGISLATIVE PAPERS
  - Sub-Series A: General Assembly Session 1960-1961
    - General July-November 1959 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 1)
    - General, December 1959 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 2)
    - General January 1-15, 1960 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 3)
    - General January 16-31, 1960 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 4)
    - General February 1-15, 1960 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 5)
    - General February 16-29, 1960 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 6)
    - General March 1960 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 7)
    - General April 1960 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 8)
    - General May-August 1960 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 9)
    - General September-December 1960 (Box-folder Box 129, Folder 10)
    - General, 1959-1960 (undated) (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia - Reports by Miscellaneous Agencies 1955-1960 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia - House Documents 4~2-7 (Reports by Various Agencies) 1959 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia - House Documents #8-11,3-21, 23-24 - Reports by Various Agencies 1959 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia - Senate Documents #1, 3-12 - Reports by Various Agencies 1959-1960 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 5)
    - General Assembly - Notes on Legislative Procedure 1958 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 6)
    - General Assembly - Cumulative Index of Bills and Resolutions Introduced through February 25,1960 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 7)
    - General Assembly Bills January-March 1960 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Accountants (C.P.A.) - House Bill #25 Correspondence 1959-1960 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Billboards, Regulation of, Correspondence 1959-1960 (Box-folder Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Credit Unions - House Bill #215 Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Education (General) Correspondence; Miscellaneous Materials 1959-1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Education (Old Dominion University) Correspondence; Miscellaneous Materials 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Education - State Dept. of Education Correspondence; Miscellaneous Materials, 1959-1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Education - Virginia Education Association; Miscellaneous Materials 1958-1959 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Education - Virginia Education Association; Miscellaneous Materials 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Fire Fighters' Bill - Correspondence February 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Gun Control Bill - Correspondence March 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Howell "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Bill - Correspondence December 1959 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Howell "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Bill - Text of Bill January 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Howell "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Bill - Correspondence, January 1-10, 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Howell "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Bill - Correspondence January 1-10, 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Howell "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Bill - Correspondence;Editorials January 21-31, 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Howell "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Bill - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Materials February-September 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Howell "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Bill - Re: Alcoholic Beverage Laws (State of Maryland) January 1960 (Box-folder Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Ports in Virginia (especially Tidewater) - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Materials 1959-1960 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Sales Tax - Correspondence 1959-1960 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Self-Insurance by the State of Virginia (House Bill #341) - Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 3)
    - State Budget - Miscellaneous Materials 1960 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Sunday Closing Bill - Correspondence 1959-1960 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 5)
    - General January - March, 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 6)
    - General April 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 7)
    - General May-June, 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 8)
    - General July-December 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Education - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Education - Virginia Education Association - Miscellaneous Material, 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Equal Opportunity (for Blacks) - Miscellaneous Material 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Health and Welfare - Correspondence 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Howell "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Bill - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1961 (Box-folder Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series B: General Assembly Session 1962-1963
    - General (Howell not Re-elected to Legislature) January-June 1962 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 1)
    - General (Howell not Re-elected to Legislature), July-December 1962 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material (Howell a Candidate in Democratic Primary) January-June 1963 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material (Howell Victorious in July Democratic Primary) July-October 1963 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Howell Victorious in November General Election) November 1963 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material (Howell Elected in November) December 1963 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Education (Includes V.E.A. Material), 1963 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Health and Welfare Correspondence, 1963 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 8)
    - "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material 1963 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Poll Tax: Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material 1963 Sub-Series C: 1964-1965 General Assembly Session (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Materials January 1-15, 1964 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence January 16-31, 1964 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 12)
    - General, February 1-15, 1964 (Box-folder Box 133, Folder 13)
  - General Assembly Session 1964-1965
    - General, February 16-29, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 1)
    - General, March, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 2)
    - General, April-August, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 3)
    - General, September-December, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 4)
    - General Assembly - Text of Bills, January-February, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 5)
    - General Assembly - Calendar and Bills and Resolutions Referred - House, Senate (Incomplete), January-March, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights Bill of 1964 - Miscellaneous Material, January - March, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Redistricting in Virginia - Correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Sarah Constant Shrine (Park) Controversy - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, January-February, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Consumer Affairs (especially Utilities Regulation) Correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Education (General), 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Education (Norfolk State College), January-March, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Education (Old Dominion University), January-April, 1964 (Box-folder Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Education (Tuition Grants) Correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Equal Opportunity (for Blacks) Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, January-March, 1964 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Health and Welfare - General Correspondence; Miscellaneous Materials, 1964 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Health and Welfare - Miscellaneous Publications, 1963 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 4)
    - "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Correspondence, January-February, 1964 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Poll Tax Correspondence, January-March, 1964 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 6)
    - General, January, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 7)
    - General, February, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 8)
    - General, March, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 9)
    - General, April, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 10)
    - General, May, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 11)
    - General, June, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 12)
    - General, July, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 13)
    - General, August, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 14)
    - General, September, 1965 (Box-folder Box 135, Folder 15)
    - General, October, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 1)
    - General, November, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 2)
    - General, December, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Auto Insurance (General), January-June, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Auto Insurance (General), July-December, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Auto Insurance - Cancellations Correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Redistricting (Va.), January-June, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Redistricting (Va.), July-August, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Congressional Redistricting (Va.), September-December, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Consumer Affairs - General Correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Consumer Affairs - Materials from Senator Paul Douglas (Illinois), 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Consumer Affairs - Virginia Consumer Protection Agency Correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Education (General) Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Equal Opportunity - Civil Rights Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Health and Welfare - General Correspondence- Miscellaneous Material, 1965 (Box-folder Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Health and Welfare (Norfolk Public Health Hospital) Correspondence, February-August, 1965 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Health and Welfare - State Report of the Virginia Mental Retardation Planning Council, December 31, 1965 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 2)
    - "Liquor-by-the-Drink" - Miscellaneous Material, 1965 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Poll Tax Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1965 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Texts of Legislative Bills (Miscellaneous), August, 1965 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 5)
    - General, January 1-15, 1966 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 6)
    - General, January 16-31, 1966 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 7)
    - General, February, 1966 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 8)
    - General, March 1-20, 1966 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 9)
    - General, March 21-31, 1966 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 10)
    - General, April 1-20, 1966 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 11)
    - General, April 21-30, 1966 (Box-folder Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series D: General Assembly Session 1966-1967
    - General, May-July, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 1)
    - General, August, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 2)
    - General, September, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 3)
    - General, October, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 4)
    - General, November, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 5)
    - General, December, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Auto Insurance (General) Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Auto Insurance - Cancellations; Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 8)